let's take a look at some of the phones
are used this was my first one it was
there
Nokia any idea what the name is it was
called Nokia two one zero zero it costs
me Rhonda six thousand rupees around a
hundred dollars
not many stores were are selling this so
I had to go to a special store to get
this it was in 2003 and I used it for
eight months by the end of it ah I was
pretty good at using it I produced the
phone quite fast by just using the
number keypad rather than using the
minnow Dana and I had quite a few
features madam it was mostly calls and
SMS battery lasted a total three days
though so that was nice
so the next one was the Sony Ericsson
phone which had a color screen it was
called Sony Ericsson T 630
it cost me around 8000 rupees or around
120 dollars the box is this one scheme
could be compared to what we get now
this phone had a camera even though it
was very tiny though I used it for a one
and a half year it was in 2004 and this
also had quite a few games to the color
screen was a quite impressive for the
time though the joystick controller and
the medulla eventually broke by the time
I was done with it next came the Nokia
phone this had both the front facing and
the back facing camera
the back cameras can load a different
camera was pretty useless never they
wouldn't use it for anything
even though they promised to video chat
the network was not that good at the
time Kazmir andhe 15,000 rupees or
around two hundred and twenty five
dollars it had quite an impressive
screen which was a way to me and the
camera on the back was also good for the
time I bought this in 2005 used it for a
one and a half year gonna really like
this phone it was a windows mobile phone
called a dope eight one eight pro it
came with the stylus window see I was
quite crappy to use but uh it was
amazing what you can do on this phone it
had the start button and my nose and
everything it was quite fun to use
though I paid around 23,000 or around
three hundred and forty four apiece I
bought it in 2000 so I used it for 11
months and it was eventually replaced
way yep the iPhone this was something
now magical micron believer how slitty
you a and the phone was you and it had
no apps it worked quite amazingly
everyone I showed this to was a quite
impressed the pinch and zoom was a kind
of a amazing to experience and see I
have to jailbreak it to make it work in
India
and cost me around 27,000 or around $400
it was really crazy and there's none of
these shops out selling it so I had to
go to a special store to get it
I bought it in a 2007 few months after
launch used it for a two years it was
really fun to use it
I'm tada using - I was quite tired of
water jailbreaking so I switched to
Android and got this our HTC Hero and
quite a few widgets paid about 3200 for
this or around four hundred and seventy
five dollars it was in 2009 used it for
11 months
you will customize it a lot I wanted a
really good camera so I got this Samsung
ultra touch it had a 16 megapixel camera
paid about 15,000 rupees or around 225
dollars the phone was really slow to use
and the interface was quite bad even
though it could take good photos it was
quite hard to do anything with those
photos even copying them was quite a
hard thing to do and that widget
interface was a quite horrible to use mm
name I only used it for one month and
tried something new look quite businessí
and cool I really wanted to use the
chatting app none of my friends had it
so nobody used it really like the
keyboard Oh operating system was a
really bad
cost me around 16,000 rupees or around
200 Anna $34 this was in 2009 only used
it for two months and give it to me it
needed a special email and Internet
connections interface to set it up was
also really bad you have to reset it
quite a few times so I went early gave
up
and when tour Windows Mobile but the HTC
hd7 I really like the pad interface this
was the first version of Windows Mobile
so it was really painful to use the
interface was a queen put but there were
no apps none of the major apps wearable
on the platform cost me around thirty
thousand three hundred or around four
hundred and fifty dollars but this in
I still use red for eight months then I
got the Samsung Galaxy s2 it was a
really good phone with quite a nice
screen it was really fast - paid about
thirty thousand six hundred four hundred
and fifty five dollars used it for
seventeen months you know 2011 I gave
this up after two years because it never
got any updates then I went oh my phone
five didn't need any jailbreaks
so it was really fun to use worked
really well
we had about 45 thousand around six
hundred and seventy dollars I bought it
in 2013 and used it for two years then
both the iPhone 6 this was the perfect
phone nice screen very nice design and
the minimal was really nice
paid about 53,000 around seven hundred
and ninety dollars quite pricey though
bought it in 2014
used it for 19 months before in broke
then I had to travel for a few days so I
desperately needed a phone so I got this
some cheap Sam's and guru it was quite a
would phone the battery lasted out more
than a week but you could only use it
for the Carleton messaging though but a
really tiny phone and pretty impressive
battery paid about 1200 rupees or around
$20 or so used it for a one month you
know 2016 then I got this cheap Android
phone called a did me to play the
interface looks quite a close to water
apples UI drops like really nice specs
for the price I paid about seven
thousand rupees
water on down 110 dollars this is pay
Tommy used it for a one month in 2016 I
switched to this life wind for only
because now it came with a free 4G SIM
and free internet for six months paid
about 8500 or around 125 dollars I'm
still using this for a free 4G internet
it's been nearly eight months I really
used this one I was only using the 4G
hotspot on this phone I only bought this
phone because that was the only way to
get the three 4G internet I wanted to
buy the iPhone 7 but I got the iPhone 7
plus just for the camera I think the
iPhone salmon would have been the
perfect sized phone because the 7 plus
is quite big paid about a 72 thousand
rupees
around $1,075 but this in 2017 this is
the same place really nice one can't
wait to see what's out there quite nice
check it out let's take a look at these
emoji train depends the color of the pen
dimensions think inside you can get this
in our quite a few colors costs around
80 rupees or around dollar and fifty
cents or so
and as a toe tips one is this our video
tip you had a really tiny one you can
sketch with one and paint with one
really nicely designed pin when you're
using this edge you cannot store the
camper now the same when you are using
this site you can also store the kappa
on the other end really nice this is the
other model this is Modena Japan it was
under fire Japanese yen all around
ninety rupees two dollars or so this is
the first time our Sinha any kind of
branding on a pin I don't know if you
can see it's in our red letters it says
a zebra and on the other side it says
Japan
that on one end looks
that's tethered
really nice color you can also store the
camp on the other end same with this one
also
that's the sketch inside I think you can
refill them but uh I'm not sure this
hunter comes in many different colors
again the pen color matches the ink
inside witness check let's take a look
at this joyful pencil box this is
general Safari you would have be sure of
an animal on top with some interesting
facts about it there were quite a few
animals to choose from the tiger
panthera tigris is their largest cat
species reaching a total body length of
up to 11 feet and weighing up to 360
ages interesting idea to put facts on
the box you would have freescale pencil
and eraser and a timetable and you also
get a sliding tray where you can store
pencils and pens and you also get two
extra spaces
you can store a sharpness or a pencil
it's there even are in Griffins can be
put in this space this box costs around
70 rupees or around a dollar or so each
animal gets hand different color quite
nice trigger hello well let's take a
look at the ballast and um craft kit
this is a sand on parted in three
bottles and colored sand and that's how
it looks once it's done because around
550 rupees around twelve dollars and
that's how those are the instructions
let me open the case for you or they set
for you this is what you get with the
kit
you're getting a small funnel with the
kit you're also getting a small spoon
you get three bottles and cokes to close
the top even though the bottles feel
like they have a glass bottom these are
plastic bottles so they're quite safe to
use it's breaking them and three of them
are uniquely shaped so making the that's
you can let your imagination run wild
this is like a sticker that you use to
level this and once it's inside the
bottle by using the it's just sand
colored into that color and I am
possible in the whole process it's quite
fun and relaxed quite nicely
[Music]
it took me about 10 minutes to do this
you really need to use all the tools
they give you to get the
I walk in place you can let your
imagination run wild and use any colors
you like and thank you for watching the
video don't forget to click the like
button subscribe to get more videos
every day